wishesmessages.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy – WishesMessages.com

WishesMessages.com respects the privacy of its visitors and strives to give users an enjoyable and safe browsing experience. At all times we strive to ensure that we remain compliant to the latest rules and regulations including the newest European General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). By using the website, you consent to the data and information practices set out in this user friendly privacy policy.

**Collection of information**  
**Analytics**  
Like most other websites, we use tools and third party applications to monitor traffic and site usage. These analytical tools may keep a log of visitor activity on the website by collecting non-personal information such as IP addresses, device types, landing pages, browser types, demographics and engagement statistics for website content.

Advanced analytical tools including but not limited to Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may also gather information about audience demographics and interests via cookies and anonymous identifiers. This is a standard practice for most online publishing websites however you may opt-out of the same by learning more about it at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

**Cookies and 3 rd Party Advertisements**

A cookie is a piece of text data sent from a website to a user’s web browser. Cookies are generally used to allow web servers to personalize browsing experience. The website along with its analytics and advertising partners may use cookies to enhance browsing experience, a practice that most standard websites engage in. Most web browsers accept cookies but you can usually change your browser settings if you prefer to refuse cookies.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to the site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/.

Third party ad providers including Google may show personalized ads to users across the world including the EEA. Such personalized ads reach users based on interests, demographics and other criteria. We highly encourage you to go through the official guidelines issued by Google regarding information collected from personalized ads https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites

**Security**

We try our best to ensure a safe browsing environment by using industry standard hosting, publishing platforms and tools. Various electronic and operational procedures are also in place to prevent unauthorized access to the website and its infrastructure.

**Links to other websites**  
WishesMessages.com may contain links to other websites or services. We are not responsible for privacy, security or any other issues directly or indirectly related to your online activities once you leave this website.

**Limitations to privacy**

We will not be responsible for data and information practices of advertising partners and third party applications. We will not be held responsible for any losses or damages caused by your online activities. Although we try our best to deliver a safe browsing environment, your privacy and online safety is ultimately your responsibility due to the inherent risks of the internet and related data transmission. To find out more about how you can stay safe online, please click [here](http://www.google.com/goodtoknow/online-safety/).

**Changes**  
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy any time by updating this page. Please check this page for updates. Last updated: 4 June 2018

**Contact**  
If you have any queries, please [contact us](https://wishesmessages.com/contact-us).
